# CLAUDIA GUERRA BAK

## QUALITY ASSURANCE | ASPIRING WEB DEVELOPER

 $\lozenge \operatorname{Leeds}$ 

Right to work in the UK

07394040635

www.claudiaguerrabak.com

in <u>claudiaguerrabak</u>

### **PROFILE**

A Quality Assurance Professional with 5 years of experience. I have recently completed a Web Development course, adding skills in HTML, CSS, React and more to my expertise in software testing. I am organised and methodical, with an eye for detail, logical thinking, strong communication skills, and a solid work ethic. I believe in doing things right, maintaining high standards. I'm always ready to assist my colleagues and share my knowledge to help the team succeed.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Quality Assurance Consultant Oracle**

August 2022 - April 2024

I worked in the implementation of Energy&Water products such as C2M, CCS, and CC&B. In different stages of testing, such as System Testing, Regression Testing, System Integration Testing and User Acceptance Testing. My main activities consisted of the following:

- · Test execution, design and planning, as well as maintaining existing test cases
- Identification, documentation, and tracking of defects using Jira
- Implementation of new projects in collaboration with software development and design teams
- Creation of training materials, templates, and simulations to accelerate new employee onboarding

## **Software Validation Tech**

January 2015 - October 2017

## Intel

- Manual and Automated test cases execution for Intel Graphics, focusing on display, media, and rendering components
- · Identification, documentation, and tracking of defects using Jira
- Creation of comprehensive documentation for new platforms and training material on testing procedures
- Participated as point of contact for Android projects, utilising Linux environments

## **COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS**

## **Web Development & Cloud Computing**

Junior Achievement Americas

May 2024 - October 2024

• The topics covered during this course include Programming Foundations, Web Design, HTML, CSS, React and AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification.

## **AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner... in progress**

Amazon

Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Certified Foundations Associate
Oracle

2023

2024

## SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Git/GitHub
- React
- Jira
- SoapUI

### SOFT SKILLS

- Attention to Detail
- Teamwork
- Communication
- Proactive
- Adaptability
- Work Ethic
- Leadership

#### EDUCATION

Physics 2017-2023 Universidad de Guadalajara

#### LANGUAGES

English C1Spanish Native